(Penny:)- All right?
- All right.
(Penny:)Oh, my God,
would you just get off my case?
(Penny:)- Weird.
- Oh, good.
(Sheldon:)That was an unusual interaction.
I wasn't sure.
(Leonard:)- You guys have an argument?
- No.
(Leonard:)You clearly did something
to aggravate her.
SHELDON:
I'm at a loss.
(Sheldon:)If you like, you can review my daily log
of social interactions...
(Sheldon:)...and see if there's a blunder
I overlooked.
(Leonard:)Here you go.
Oh, you owe me another $2.
The price of moo shu pork went up.
[SIGHS]
(Howard:)It's getting tougher and tougher
to be a bad Jew.
(Leonard:)Here you go, Penny.
Shrimp with lobster sauce.
Thank you. What's my share?
- Uh, don't worry about it. It's my treat.
- No, really. How much?
It's whatever. Ten, $11.
Well, which is it? Ten or 11?
Fourteen-fifty. But it's no biggie.
(Leonard:)You'll get the next one.
[BOTH LAUGH]
(Penny:)What?